[
{"type":"header","version":"4.9.2","comment":"Export to JSON plugin for PHPMyAdmin"},
{"type":"database","name":"school"},
{"type":"table","name":"inpr","database":"school","data":
[
{"no":"1","question":"Is a variable that stores\/points the address of another variable.","answer":"Pointer","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"2","question":"Is used to allocate memory dynamically at run time & it also might belong to any of the data type.","answer":"Pointers","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"3","question":"It is a variable whose value is the address of another variable.","answer":"Pointers","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"4","question":"Symbol used to denote a pointer Variable","answer":"*","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"5","question":"It is the symbol used to access the address of the variable","answer":"&","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"6","question":"This Symbol is also called as Reference Operator","answer":"&","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"7","question":"Give the Printf Format (Format Specifier) to output variable address into a hexa decimal","answer":"%x","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"8","question":"when we increment or decrement pointer, it is now called the process of ____ ______","answer":"Pointer Arithmetic","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"9","question":"It define arrays to hold a number of pointers","answer":"Array of Pointers","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"10","question":"It is another user-defined data type available in C that allows to combine different kinds.","answer":"Structure","exam":"midterm","lesson":"1"},
{"no":"11","question":"Are used to represent a record like students record, book record, employees record, etc.","answer":"Structure","exam":"midterm","lesson":"2"},
{"no":"12","question":"Is used to define a structure. It defines new data type, with more than one member","answer":"Struct Statement","exam":"midterm","lesson":"2"},
{"no":"13","question":"True or False : Structure Variable can be declared with structure declaration or as a separate declaration like basic types.","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"2"},
{"no":"14","question":"True or False: Structure members can be initialized using curly braces {}?","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"2"},
{"no":"15","question":"True or False: Structure Tag is an optional and each member definition is a normal variable definition.","answer":"True","exam":"midterm","lesson":"2"},
{"no":"16","question":"In structure we use member access operator which is the symbol _ ","answer":".","exam":"midterm","lesson":"2"},
{"no":"17","question":"It is the period between the structure variable name and the structure member users wish to access.","answer":"Member Access Operator","exam":"midterm","lesson":"2"},
{"no":"18","question":"Means to feed some data into a program.","answer":"Input","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"19","question":"It can be a form of file or from the command line.","answer":"input","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"20","question":"It means to display some data on screen, printer, or in any file.","answer":"Out Put","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"21","question":"Are means to access the file for reading and writing purpose.","answer":"File pointers","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"22","question":"It returns total number of inputs scanned successfully.","answer":"printf","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"23","question":"Reads the next available character from the screen and returns it as an integer.","answer":"get char","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"24","question":"It puts the passed character on the screen and return the same character.","answer":"putchar","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"25","question":"It reads a line from std in into the buffer pointed to by s until either a terminating newline or EOF","answer":"gets","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"26","question":"This function writes the string 's' and 'a' trailing newline to stdout","answer":"Puts","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"27","question":"This function instead of printing on console store it on char buffer which are specified in s print f","answer":"String print function","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"28","question":"Is used to print the string content in file but not on stdout console","answer":"F print f","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"29","question":"Is used in C to generate random numbers","answer":"Rand function","exam":"midterm","lesson":"3"},
{"no":"30","question":"A ____ represents a sequence of bytes, regardless of being a text file or a binary file.","answer":"File","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"31","question":"A ___ represents a sequence of bytes on the disk where a group of related data is stored.","answer":"File","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"32","question":"Use the ______ function used to create a new file or to open an existing file.","answer":"fopen","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"33","question":"a function used to create a new file or to open an existing file.","answer":"fopen","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"34","question":"this function is used to close a file","answer":"fclose","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"35","question":"This function reads a character from a file","answer":"getc","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"36","question":"this function is used to write a character from a file","answer":"putc","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"37","question":"this function is used to reads a set of data from a file","answer":"fscanf","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"38","question":"this function is used to write a set of data to a file","answer":"fprintf","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"39","question":"this function is used to read an integer from a file","answer":"getw","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"40","question":"this function is used to write an integer to a file","answer":"putw","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"41","question":"this function is used to set the position to desire point","answer":"fseek","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"42","question":"This gives current position in the file","answer":"ftell","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"43","question":"This function sets the position to the beginning point","answer":"rewind","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"44","question":"___ is the name of the file to be opened and mode specifies the purpose of opening the file.","answer":"filename","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"45","question":"____ specifies the purpose of opening the file.","answer":"mode","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"46","question":"this mode open an existing file for reading mode and purpose","answer":"r","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"47","question":"this mode will opens a textfile for writing mode. if not exist then new file will be created and start writing from the beginning of the file","answer":"w","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"48","question":"This mode opens a file for writing in appending mode, if not exist then new file will be created","answer":"a","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"49","question":"this mode opens a text file for both reading and writing","answer":"r+","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"50","question":"this mode opens a text file for both reading and writing, it intruncates the file to zero length if it exist otherwise creates a file if not","answer":"w+","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"51","question":"this mode is used for both reading and writing. It creates the file if not exist. It read start from the beginning but writing can only be appended","answer":"a+","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"52","question":"this mode open a binary file for reading mode.","answer":"Rb","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"53","question":"This mode open a binary file in writing mode.","answer":"Wb","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"54","question":"This mode opens a binary file in writing mode","answer":"Wb","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"55","question":"This mode opens a binary file in append mode","answer":"Ab","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"56","question":"This mode opens a binary file in both reading and writing mode","answer":"rb+","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"57","question":"this function is used to close an already opened file. It returns zero on success or EOF if there is an error in closing the file.","answer":"fclose","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"58","question":"This function writes the string s to the output streamed reference by fp. It return a non negative value on success. otherwise EOF is returned in anycase of any error.","answer":"fputs","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"59","question":"this function directly writes into the file while fscanf reads from the file","answer":"fprintf","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"60","question":"This function is used for reading character from the input file","answer":"fgetc","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"61","question":"this function reads from n-1 character from the input stream referenced by fp","answer":"fgets","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"62","question":"How many bytes an int data type have?(Note: Do not include the word bytes || byte)","answer":"4","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"63","question":"How many bytes a char data type have?(Note: Do not include the word bytes || byte)","answer":"1","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"64","question":"How many bytes a float data type have?(Note: Do not include the word bytes || byte)","answer":"4","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"},
{"no":"65","question":"How many bytes a double data type have?(Note: Do not include the word bytes || byte)","answer":"8","exam":"midterm","lesson":"4"}
]
}
]
